BRUNO PREGUN

Zagreb, Croatia | bruno@pregun.com

SUMMARY

I am a freelance game programmer and designer with several years of professional experience in the games industry. Driven by passion for creating immersive experiences, engaging gameplay mechanics, and compelling virtual worlds and narratives.

I am based in Zagreb and currently working at <u>Cutting Edge Entertainment</u>. Concentrating on Game Design, Level Design, Technical Design, and Programming.

EXPERIENCE

Game Designer at CUTTING EDGE ENTERTAINMENT (June 2023 - Present) https://store.steampowered.com/app/2559860/Three_Goblin_Wobblin/ https://store.steampowered.com/app/3702370/A Game About Mining an Asteroid/

- Designing and developing multiple indie game projects (UE5 and Godot)
- Designing and implementing gameplay mechanics
- Modeling 3D environment art assets and level design
- Implemented an in-game level editor
- Recording and editing promotional materials (screenshots, trailers)
- Writing and maintaining game design documentation for an unannounced project

Freelance Game Engineer at YAGER (March 2022 – June 2023)

https://store.steampowered.com/app/868270/The_Cycle_Frontier/

- Developing and supporting a live service extraction shooter game in UE4
- Focus on meta/progression mechanics and UI engineering support
- Working with online infrastructure and backend platforms (Azure, Playfab)
- Implementing support for third party APIs (Twitch Drops, Gamesight)
- Working and collaborating with a diverse multicultural team

Game Programmer at GAMEPIRES (October 2017 – March 2022)

https://store.steampowered.com/app/513710/SCUM/

- Developing and supporting a multiplayer survival game in UE4
- Successfully leading a team of programmers, animators, and artists to deliver a major content update
- Designing, implementing, and monitoring gameplay features in a live multiplayer environment
- Designing and implementing UX and UI solutions for various game systems
- Authoring in-house tools for level design and art departments
- Designing materials and shaders for various special effects

SKILLS

- Programming (C++, UE4, C#, JS)
- Scripting
- Computer Graphics
- 3D Modeling (Blender)
- Tech Art

- Game Design
- Level Design
- UI Design
- Teamwork & Collaboration
- Fluent in English

SIDE PROJECTS

- Multiple unreleased gameplay protoypes (personal projects)
- Cloth and Particle Simulation using OpenGL (student project)
- Modeling and Visualization of Virtual Interiors (student project)
- Basic low-level software rasterizer using pure C code
- Custom 2D game engine for personal projects
- Simple note-taking and mind mapping javascript web app
- Several short Unreal Engine 4 games for game jams

EDUCATION

Faculty of Electrical Engineering and Computing, Zagreb, Croatia

- (2015 2017) Master's degree, Computer Science
- (2010 2015) Bachelor's degree, Computer Science

LINKS

Portfolio: burstsort.github.io/

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/bruno-pregun/

Github: github.com/burstsort/